Guide to the Cooper, Hewitt & Co. Letterpress Copybooks 1848-1905 MS 1130
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
Cooper, Hewitt & Co. letterpress copybooks
1848-1905
MS 1130
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
51.0 Linear feet in 51 record cartons
The collection includes 296 letter books containing letterpress copies of outgoing correspondence, primarily concerning the business matters of Cooper, Hewitt & Co. (1848-1905), the firm of Edward Cooper (1824-1905) and Abram Hewitt (1822-1903). The correspondence relates to Cooper and Hewitt’s activities as agents for the Trenton Iron Co. (New Jersey), managing all purchases of ore, coal, and other raw materials, all sales of finished iron, supplies of credit for current operations, daily instructions for operation, maintenance of accounts, sales of railroad rails, blooms, billets, pig iron, flats, rounds, wire for fence and bridges, iron ore, coal, administration problems, their agency for Welsh and European mill output, publicity, developments in equipment and processes, materials for gun barrels during the Civil War, development of the iron and steel industry, etc. Some letters, mostly from the 1870s and later, concern political, philanthropic, and matters other than business.
Cooper, Hewitt & Company (Ringwood, N.J.).
Immediate Source of Acquisition Note
The collection was a gift from the estate of Erskine Hewitt, via Norvin H. Green. 277 of the books were acquired on 22 November 1938 and the remaining fourteen on 29 December 1939.
Access Restrictions
Open to qualified researchers. The volumes are stored offsite so researchers need to request them one week in advance of their intended visit.
Related Archival Materials Note
Along with these copybooks, the donor, Norvin Green, provided N-YHS with other of Abram Hewitt's copybooks related to his mayoral and congressional years. At some point, these were cataloged separately, perhaps with other related material:
Diary and letterpress copybooks (1843, 1876, 1887-1888 (bulk 1887-1888)
Call phrase: BV Hewitt, Abram S.
New-York Historical Society holds much other material concerning Cooper & Hewitt, Abram Hewitt, and to a lesser extent Edward Cooper, including:
Cooper, Hewitt & Company bills, receipts, letters (1842-1921, bulk 1842-1890)
Call phrase: AHMC - Cooper, Hewitt & Company
Abram S. Hewitt collection, 1844-1901, undated
Call phrase: AHMC - Hewitt, Abram
Beyond N-YHS, the Library of Congress holds a major collection (233 linear feet) of Cooper, Hewitt & Co records:
Cooper, Hewitt & Company (Ringwood, N.J.) records, 1833-1908 (ID MSS16816)
Arrangement Note
The collection is arranged in volume number order. The volumes proceed in chronological order.
The earliest volumes, labeled C & H, are numbered 2 to 27 (volumes 1 and 19 are missing). After volume 27, the labeling changes to C.H. & Co. and the numbering starts over with 1, proceeding to the end (volume 271). This second set is missing volumes 5, 122, 236, 237, and 241.
Scope and Contents Note
The collection includes 296 letter books containing letterpress copies of outgoing correspondence, primarily concerning the business matters of Cooper, Hewitt & Co. (1848-1905), the firm of Edward Cooper and Abram Hewitt. Some letters, a small amount in relation to the whole, concern political, philanthropic, and matters other than business; these seem to date mostly from the 1870s and later. The business correspondence relates to Cooper and Hewitt’s activities as agents for the Trenton Iron Co., managing all purchases of ore, coal, and other raw materials, all sales of finished iron, supplies of credit for current operations, daily instructions for operation, maintenance of accounts, sales of railroad rails, blooms, billets, pig iron, flats, rounds, wire for fence and bridges, iron ore, coal, administration problems, their agency for Welsh and European mill output, publicity, developments in equipment and processes, materials for gun barrels during the Civil War, development of the iron and steel industry, etc.
Each of the volumes holds about 1000 sheets and most of the volumes are full. The copies can be difficult to read because of faded or blurred ink. Typed copies begin to appear in the volumes around the 1880s, and these appear to relate mostly to the non-business matters. Some of the volumes, especially the earlier ones, are somewhat deteriorated. Each of the volumes includes an index to the correspondents in the book, noting the page numbers on which that correspondent appears. Frequent correspondents include the Trenton Iron Co., New Jersey Steel & Iron Co., Pequest Iron Works (Oxford, NJ), Architectural Iron Works (14th Street in New York City), and Durham Iron Works (Riegelsville, Penn). Various corporate customers appear including railroads (e.g., Hudson River Rail Road, Morris & Essex Railroad, and New York & Harlem Railroad) and arms (e.g., Remington & Sons, Rock Island Arsenal). During the Civil War period, Alexander Brydue Dyer of the Springfield Armory (Massachusetts) appears frequently. Other notable names also appear in the indexes, including the Morris Canal Co., Jay Gould, Joseph Wharton, and the Roeblings. Researchers should be aware that only a few indexes were skimmed during processing so the above names give only a sense of the entire range of correspondents.
Only seven scattered volumes appear to be missing, so the volumes represent almost the entire history of the Edward Cooper-Abram Hewitt partnership. With Hewitt’s death in 1903, the number of entries fell off, with only about 100 pages filled by Cooper and others before the final entry in 1905.
Edward Cooper and Abram Hewitt were connected directly or indirectly to Cooper Union (Edward suceeded his father as president) and the Cooper Hewitt Smithsonian Design Museum (Abram's daughters founded it in 1895). It seems unlikely that these copybooks include any letters of substance related to those institutions, but the possibility cannot be definitively dismissed because so little of the content has been reviewed.
Biographical/Historical Note
Edward Cooper (1824-1905) met Abram Stevens Hewitt (1822-1903) at Columbia College. They became friends, graduating in 1842 and traveling together. They went into business as partners, with the financial backing of Edward’s father, Peter Cooper (1791-1883). Peter Cooper had no formal education, but had learned various trades and had a knack for invention. Working his way through trades and operating a grocery store, Peter eventually bought a glue factory in New York City in 1821. His success with this business, as well as with his invention of related gelatin products, including what is known today as Jell-O, made him an increasingly wealthy man by the mid-19th century.
By the 1830s, Peter Cooper turned his attention to iron, purchasing a mining operation (the Ringwood Company) and property in northern New Jersey. He opened an ironworks in Trenton in 1845. It was this business that Peter’s son, Edward, and future son-in-law, Abram Hewitt, took over the management of. Edward Cooper and Hewitt eventually formalized their partnership as Cooper, Hewitt & Co. They expanded the iron business to encompass an iron ore mine at Andover, NJ, and blast furnaces at Philipsburg, NJ.
In 1855, Abram Hewitt married Edward’s sister, Sarah Amelia Cooper (1830-1912). In 1856, Hewitt visited the business’s Ringwood operation, coming away impressed with both the mining resources and the beauty of the area. He returned with Sarah to the location and they adopted the house, known then and now as Ringwood Manor, as their summer home. They continued to live at other times on Lexington Avenue in New York City in Peter Cooper’s household.
In addition to the thriving iron business, by the 1870s Hewitt became active in politics. A Democrat, he was first elected to Congress in 1874. He was re-elected in 1876, lost in 1878, and re-elected in 1880, 1882, and 1884. Then leaving Congress, he was elected mayor of New York in 1886. He was defeated in 1888, ending his political career.
The Coopers and Hewitt were known for their philanthropy, especially concerning education. Peter Cooper, appreciating the value of a formal education he never had, founded Cooper Union in 1859 and remained its president until 1882. At that time, Edward Cooper became Cooper Union’s second president, remaining in the position until 1804, just before his death.
Abram Hewitt died in 1903. His 50% ownership share of the Trenton Iron Company passed into the hands of his children. Edward Cooper then sold his 50% stake to his sister, Hewitt’s widow. In 1904, the Hewitt family sold the works to the United States Steel Corporation. (See Vol. 271, pg. 516, for Cooper's reference to this transaction.) Edward Cooper died in 1905. The Ringwood Company changed in the 1920s from a mining operation into a land company, developing the municipality of Ringwood in New Jersey.
Abram and Sarah Hewitt had six children, the youngest being Erskine Hewitt (1871-1938), from whose estate came the letterpress copybooks in this collection. Sending them to N-YHS from Hewitt’s estate was his nephew, Norvin Green (1893-1955), Abram Hewitt’s grandson by his eldest child, Amelia Hewitt Green (1856-1922).
(The above note was based largely on information from the website of Ringwood Manor: www.ringwoodmanor.org.)
Cooper, Edward, 1824-1905 -- Correspondence; Cooper, Hewitt & Company (Ringwood, N.J.). -- Correspondence; Hewitt, Abram S., (Abram Stevens), 1822-1903 -- Correspondence; Trenton Iron Co..; United States. Army. -- Firearms; Business records; Commercial agents -- New York (State) -- New York; Firearms -- United States -- Design and construction; Iron industry and trade -- Europe; Iron industry and trade -- New Jersey -- Trenton; Iron industry and trade -- New York (State) -- New York; Letterpress copybooks; New York (N.Y.) -- Politics and government; Railroad rails; United States -- History -- Civil War, 1861-1865 -- Equipment and supplies; Wire industry -- New Jersey -- Trenton; Wire industry -- New York (State) -- New York
- Cooper & Hewitt Volumes (Box -)
- Volume 2, 1848 October-1849 October (Offsite-box 1)
- Volume 3, 1849 October-1850 April (Offsite-box 1)
- Volume 4, 1850 May-October (Offsite-box 1)
- Volume 5, 1850 October-1851 May (Offsite-box 2)
- Volume 6, 1851 May-September (Offsite-box 2)
- Volume 7, 1851 September-1852 January (Offsite-box 2)
- Volume 8, 1852 January-June (Offsite-box 2)
- Volume 9, 1852 June-October (Offsite-box 2)
- Volume 10, 1852 October-1853 February (Offsite-box 3)
- Volume 11, 1853 March-July (Offsite-box 3)
- Volume 12, 1853 July-October (Offsite-box 3)
- Volume 13, 1853 October-1854 February (Offsite-box 3)
- Volume 14, 1854 February-June (Offsite-box 3)
- Volume 15, 1854 June-September (Offsite-box 1)
- Volume 16, 1854 September-December (Offsite-box 1)
- Volume 17, 1854 December-1855 March (Offsite-box 1)
- Volume 18, 1855 March-May (Offsite-box 4)
- Volume 20, 1855 August-October (Offsite-box 4)
- Volume 21, 1855 October-December (Offsite-box 4)
- Volume 22, 1855 December-1856 March (Offsite-box 4)
- Volume 23, 1856 March-May (Offsite-box 4)
- Volume 24, 1856 May-August (Offsite-box 4)
- Volume 25, 1856 August-October (Offsite-box 5)
- Volume 26, 1856 October-November (Offsite-box 5)
- Volume 27, 1856 November-1857 January (Offsite-box 5)
  Scope and Contents note
  Blank at page 49 on.
- Cooper Hewitt & Co. Volumes (Box -)
- Volume 1, 1857 January-March (Offsite-box 5)
- Volume 2, 1857 April-June (Offsite-box 5)
- Volume 3, 1857 June-August (Offsite-box 5)
- Volume 4, 1857 August-October (Offsite-box 6)
- Volume 6, 1858 February-May (Offsite-box 6)
- Volume 7, 1858 May-September (Offsite-box 6)
- Volume 8, 1858 September-December (Offsite-box 6)
- Volume 9, 1859 January-April (Offsite-box 6)
- Volume 10, 1859 April-July (Offsite-box 6)
- Volume 11, 1859 July-October (Offsite-box 7)
- Volume 12, 1859 October-1860 January (Offsite-box 7)
- Volume 13, 1860 January-April (Offsite-box 7)
- Volume 14, 1860 April-June (Offsite-box 7)
- Volume 15, 1860 June-September (Offsite-box 7)
- Volume 16, 1860 September-December (Offsite-box 7)
- Volume 17, 1860 December-1861 March (Offsite-box 8)
- Volume 18, 1861 March-July (Offsite-box 8)
- Volume 19, 1861 July-November (Offsite-box 8)
- Volume 20, 1861 November-1862 March (Offsite-box 8)
- Volume 21, 1862 March-June (Offsite-box 8)
- Volume 22, 1862 June-September (Offsite-box 8)
- Volume 23, 1862 September-November (Offsite-box 9)
- Volume 24, 1862 November-1863 February (Offsite-box 9)
- Volume 25, 1863 February-April (Offsite-box 9)
- Volume 26, 1863 April-June (Offsite-box 9)
- Volume 27, 1863 June-August (Offsite-box 9)
- Volume 28, 1863 August-October (Offsite-box 9)
- Volume 29, 1863 October-December (Offsite-box 10)
- Volume 30, 1864 January-March (Offsite-box 10)
- Volume 31, 1864 March-May (Offsite-box 10)
- Volume 32, 1864 May-December (Offsite-box 10)
- Volume 33, 1864 December-1865 May (Offsite-box 10)
- Volume 34, 1865 May-1866 February (Offsite-box 10)
- Volume 35, 1866 February-July (Offsite-box 11)
- Volume 36, 1866 July-October (Offsite-box 11)
- Volume 37, 1866 October-1867 January (Offsite-box 11)
- Volume 38, 1867 January-May (Offsite-box 11)
- Volume 39, 1867 May-August (Offsite-box 11)
- Volume 40, 1867 August-November (Offsite-box 11)
- Volume 41, 1867 November-1868 February (Offsite-box 12)
- Volume 42, 1868 February-April (Offsite-box 12)
- Volume 43, 1868 April-July (Offsite-box 12)
- Volume 44, 1868 July-September (Offsite-box 12)
- Volume 45, 1868 September-December (Offsite-box 12)
- Volume 46, 1868 December-1869 February (Offsite-box 12)
- Volume 47, 1869 February-May (Offsite-box 13)
- Volume 48, 1869 May-August (Offsite-box 13)
- Volume 49, 1869 August-December (Offsite-box 13)
- Volume 50, 1869 December-1870 March (Offsite-box 13)
- Volume 51, 1870 March-June (Offsite-box 13)
- Volume 52, 1870 June-September (Offsite-box 13)
- Volume 53, 1870 September-December (Offsite-box 13)
- Volume 54, 1870 December-1871 February (Offsite-box 14)
- Volume 55, 1871 February-May (Offsite-box 14)
- Volume 56, 1871 May-July (Offsite-box 14)
- Volume 57, 1871 July-September (Offsite-box 14)
- Volume 58, 1871 September-November (Offsite-box 14)
- Volume 59, 1871 November-1872 January (Offsite-box 14)
- Volume 60, 1872 January-March (Offsite-box 14)
- Volume 61, 1872 March-May (Offsite-box 15)
- Volume 62, 1872 May-July (Offsite-box 15)
- Volume 63, 1872 July-September (Offsite-box 15)
- Volume 64, 1872 September-November (Offsite-box 15)
- Volume 65, 1872 November-1873 February (Offsite-box 15)
- Volume 66, 1873 February-April (Offsite-box 15)
- Volume 67, 1873 April-June (Offsite-box 16)
- Volume 68, 1873 June-August (Offsite-box 16)
- Volume 69, 1873 August-October (Offsite-box 16)
- Volume 70, 1873 October-1874 January (Offsite-box 16)
- Volume 71, 1874 January-April (Offsite-box 16)
- Volume 72, 1874 April-July (Offsite-box 17)
- Volume 73, 1874 July-October (Offsite-box 17)
- Volume 74, 1874 October-1875 January (Offsite-box 17)
- Volume 75, 1875 January-April (Offsite-box 17)
- Volume 76, 1875 April-June (Offsite-box 17)
- Volume 77, 1875 June-September (Offsite-box 18)
- Volume 78, 1875 September-December (Offsite-box 18)
- Volume 79, 1875 December-1876 March (Offsite-box 18)
- Volume 80, 1876 March-June (Offsite-box 18)
- Volume 81, 1876 June-October (Offsite-box 18)
- Volume 82, 1876 October-December (Offsite-box 19)
- Volume 83, 1876 December-1877 March (Offsite-box 19)
- Volume 84, 1877 March-June (Offsite-box 19)
- Volume 85, 1877 June-September (Offsite-box 19)
- Volume 86, 1877 September-November (Offsite-box 19)
- Volume 87, 1877 November-1878 February (Offsite-box 20)
- Volume 88, 1878 February-April (Offsite-box 20)
- Volume 89, 1878 April-June (Offsite-box 20)
- Volume 90, 1878 July-September (Offsite-box 20)
- Volume 91, 1878 September-November (Offsite-box 20)
- Volume 92, 1878 November-1879 February (Offsite-box 21)
- Volume 93, 1879 February-April (Offsite-box 21)
- Volume 94, 1879 April-June (Offsite-box 21)
- Volume 95, 1879 June-August (Offsite-box 21)
- Volume 96, 1879 August-September (Offsite-box 21)
- Volume 97, 1879 September-November (Offsite-box 22)
- Volume 98, 1879 November-December (Offsite-box 22)
- Volume 99, 1879 December-1880 February (Offsite-box 22)
- Volume 100, 1880 February-March (Offsite-box 22)
- Volume 101, 1880 March-April (Offsite-box 22)
- Volume 102, 1880 April-June (Offsite-box 23)
- Volume 103, 1880 June-July (Offsite-box 23)
- Volume 104, 1880 July-September (Offsite-box 23)
- Volume 105, 1880 September-November (Offsite-box 23)
- Volume 106, 1880 November-December (Offsite-box 23)
- Volume 107, 1880 December-1881 February (Offsite-box 23)
- Volume 108, 1881 February-March (Offsite-box 24)
- Volume 109, 1881 March-April (Offsite-box 24)
- Volume 110, 1881 April-June (Offsite-box 24)
- Volume 111, 1881 June-July (Offsite-box 24)
- Volume 112, 1881 July-September (Offsite-box 24)
- Volume 113, 1881 September-October (Offsite-box 24)
- Volume 114, 1881 October-November (Offsite-box 25)
- Volume 115, 1881 November-December (Offsite-box 25)
- Volume 116, 1882 January-February (Offsite-box 25)
- Volume 117, 1882 February-March (Offsite-box 25)
- Volume 118, 1882 March-May (Offsite-box 25)
- Volume 119, 1882 May-June (Offsite-box 25)
- Volume 120, 1882 June-July (Offsite-box 26)
- Volume 121, 1882 July-September (Offsite-box 26)
- Volume 123, 1882 October-December (Offsite-box 26)
- Volume 124, 1882 December-1883 January (Offsite-box 26)
- Volume 125, 1883 January-March (Offsite-box 26)
- Volume 126, 1883 March-April (Offsite-box 26)
- Volume 127, 1883 April-May (Offsite-box 27)
- Volume 128, 1883 May-June (Offsite-box 27)
- Volume 129, 1883 June-August (Offsite-box 27)
- Volume 130, 1883 August-September (Offsite-box 27)
- Volume 131, 1883 September-November (Offsite-box 27)
- Volume 132, 1883 November-December (Offsite-box 28)
- Volume 133, 1883 December-1884 February (Offsite-box 28)
- Volume 134, 1884 February-April (Offsite-box 28)
- Volume 135, 1884 April-May (Offsite-box 28)
- Volume 136, 1884 May-July (Offsite-box 28)
- Volume 137, 1884 July-August (Offsite-box 29)
- Volume 138, 1884 August-October (Offsite-box 29)
- Volume 139, 1884 October-November (Offsite-box 29)
- Volume 140, 1884 November-December (Offsite-box 29)
- Volume 141, 1884 December-1885 February (Offsite-box 29)
- Volume 142, 1885 February-March (Offsite-box 30)
- Volume 143, 1885 March-April (Offsite-box 30)
- Volume 144, 1885 April-May (Offsite-box 30)
- Volume 145, 1885 May-June (Offsite-box 30)
- Volume 146, 1885 June-August (Offsite-box 30)
- Volume 147, 1885 August-September (Offsite-box 30)
- Volume 148, 1885 September-October (Offsite-box 31)
- Volume 149, 1885 October-November (Offsite-box 31)
- Volume 150, 1885 November-December (Offsite-box 31)
- Volume 151, 1885 December-1886 January (Offsite-box 31)
- Volume 152, 1886 January-March (Offsite-box 31)
- Volume 153, 1886 March-April (Offsite-box 32)
- Volume 154, 1886 April-May (Offsite-box 32)
- Volume 155, 1886 May-June (Offsite-box 32)
- Volume 156, 1886 June-July (Offsite-box 32)
- Volume 157, 1886 July-August (Offsite-box 32)
- Volume 158, 1886 August-September (Offsite-box 33)
- Volume 159, 1886 September-October (Offsite-box 33)
- Volume 160, 1886 October-November (Offsite-box 33)
- Volume 161, 1886 November-1887 January (Offsite-box 33)
- Volume 162, 1887 January-February (Offsite-box 33)
- Volume 163, 1887 February-March (Offsite-box 34)
- Volume 164, 1887 March-April (Offsite-box 34)
- Volume 165, 1887 April-May (Offsite-box 34)
- Volume 166, 1887 May-June (Offsite-box 34)
- Volume 167, 1887 June (Offsite-box 34)
- Volume 168, 1887 June-August (Offsite-box 35)
- Volume 169, 1887 August (Offsite-box 35)
- Volume 170, 1887 August-September (Offsite-box 35)
- Volume 171, 1887 September-October (Offsite-box 35)
- Volume 172, 1887 October-November (Offsite-box 35)
- Volume 173, 1887 November-1888 January (Offsite-box 35)
- Volume 174, 1888 January-February (Offsite-box 36)
- Volume 175, 1888 February-March (Offsite-box 36)
- Volume 176, 1888 March-April (Offsite-box 36)
- Volume 177, 1888 April-May (Offsite-box 36)
- Volume 178, 1888 May-July (Offsite-box 36)
- Volume 179, 1888 July-September (Offsite-box 36)
- Volume 180, 1888 September-November (Offsite-box 37)
- Volume 181, 1888 November-1889 January (Offsite-box 37)
- Volume 182, 1889 January-March (Offsite-box 37)
- Volume 183, 1889 March-April (Offsite-box 37)
- Volume 184, 1889 April-June (Offsite-box 37)
- Volume 185, 1889 June-August (Offsite-box 37)
- Volume 186, 1889 August-September (Offsite-box 38)
- Volume 187, 1889 September-November (Offsite-box 38)
- Volume 188, 1889 November-December (Offsite-box 38)
- Volume 189, 1889 December-1890 February (Offsite-box 38)
- Volume 190, 1890 February-March (Offsite-box 38)
- Volume 191, 1890 March-May (Offsite-box 38)
- Volume 192, 1890 May-June (Offsite-box 39)
- Volume 193, 1890 June-August (Offsite-box 39)
- Volume 194, 1890 August-October (Offsite-box 39)
- Volume 195, 1890 October-November (Offsite-box 39)
- Volume 196, 1890 November-1891 January (Offsite-box 39)
- Volume 197, 1891 January-February (Offsite-box 39)
- Volume 198, 1891 February-March (Offsite-box 40)
- Volume 199, 1891 March-May (Offsite-box 40)
- Volume 200, 1891 May-June (Offsite-box 40)
- Volume 201, 1891 June-August (Offsite-box 40)
- Volume 202, 1891 August-September (Offsite-box 40)
- Volume 203, 1891 September-November (Offsite-box 40)
- Volume 204, 1891 November-December (Offsite-box 41)
- Volume 205, 1891 December-1892 February (Offsite-box 41)
- Volume 206, 1892 February-March (Offsite-box 41)
- Volume 207, 1892 March-May (Offsite-box 41)
- Volume 208, 1892 May-June (Offsite-box 41)
- Volume 209, 1892 June-August (Offsite-box 41)
- Volume 210, 1892 August-September (Offsite-box 42)
- Volume 211, 1892 September-November (Offsite-box 42)
- Volume 212, 1892 November-December (Offsite-box 42)
- Volume 213, 1892 December-1893 January (Offsite-box 42)
- Volume 214, 1893 January-March (Offsite-box 42)
- Volume 215, 1893 March-April (Offsite-box 42)
- Volume 216, 1893 May-June (Offsite-box 43)
- Volume 217, 1893 June-August (Offsite-box 43)
- Volume 218, 1893 August-September (Offsite-box 43)
- Volume 219, 1893 September-November (Offsite-box 43)
- Volume 220, 1893 November-1894 January (Offsite-box 43)
- Volume 221, 1894 January-March (Offsite-box 43)
- Volume 222, 1894 March-May (Offsite-box 44)
- Volume 223, 1894 May-August (Offsite-box 44)
- Volume 224, 1894 August-October (Offsite-box 44)
- Volume 225, 1894 October-1895 January (Offsite-box 44)
- Volume 226, 1895 January-March (Offsite-box 44)
- Volume 227, 1895 March-May (Offsite-box 44)
- Volume 228, 1895 May-August (Offsite-box 45)
- Volume 229, 1895 August-October (Offsite-box 45)
- Volume 230, 1895 October-December (Offsite-box 45)
- Volume 231, 1895 December-1896 February (Offsite-box 45)
- Volume 232, 1896 February-April (Offsite-box 45)
- Volume 233, 1896 April-June (Offsite-box 45)
- Volume 234, 1896 June-August (Offsite-box 45)
- Volume 235, 1896 August-November (Offsite-box 46)
- Volume 238, 1897 April-June (Offsite-box 46)
- Volume 239, 1897 June-September (Offsite-box 46)
- Volume 240, 1897 September-December (Offsite-box 46)
- Volume 242, 1898 February-May (Offsite-box 46)
- Volume 243, 1898 May-July (Offsite-box 46)
- Volume 244, 1898 July-October (Offsite-box 47)
- Volume 245, 1898 October-December (Offsite-box 47)
- Volume 246, 1898 December-1899 March (Offsite-box 47)
- Volume 247, 1899 March-April (Offsite-box 47)
- Volume 248, 1899 April-June (Offsite-box 47)
- Volume 249, 1899 June-August (Offsite-box 47)
- Volume 250, 1899 August-September (Offsite-box 48)
- Volume 251, 1899 September-November (Offsite-box 48)
- Volume 252, 1899 November-December (Offsite-box 48)
- Volume 253, 1899 December-1900 February (Offsite-box 48)